So, the importance of this notochord, we see this kind of notochordal wave
that develops,
this neural tube that is completely influenced by my notochord.
In fact, it is quite important to realize that this notochord will
emit,
among other things, what we call sonic systems S-H,
so with carotene, which are significant phenomena.
Quite important in terms of induction,
especially with beta-carotene already,
vitamin A will already be integrated with this carotene,
which is very important for the eye,
with retinoic acid, which will be important at this level,
with these major genes involved.
Imagine I have my notochordal axis.
I have my developing neural tube around it.
Okay? It's developing.
We know this notochordal axis will give positional information
through an electromagnetic field,
like a GPS for the surrounding cells
to stimulate proteins.
That’s the brain part.
The eyes will develop there.
There you go, you are well positioned in this space.
Those will be the eyes, here.
And so I have an axis here, and you, you are on another plane, you
will form the foot, but in fact,
regarding the axis here, the information you receive about the midline
will differ depending on space and time.
And so, we know that this notochordal axis emits an electric field that
occurs between left and right, and between front and back.
This has been measured. Imagine this axis here, and now I enter the nodal flow.
So I am in the axis where I have this notochord.
And there, above, there are tiny cells rotating.
Imagine here, there’s snow falling.
And I have these cilia rotating all around, at the moment this notochord is forming,
which is busy transmitting a lot of micro-information,
to the left.
And which, there...
which lateralizes the embryo, actually.
This means that there is no symmetry; there is only harmony.
All genetic information is structured according to this notochord.
You are cells; if you are cells, it means you are molecules,
if you are molecules, it means proteins will form and exit.
Well, these are informations coming from your genome,
that will release, hey, you, you are in space-time, sonic.
Space-time, PAX,
all these genes will emerge.
The wool is placed here,
with all these genes that will be there,
but what I want to explain to you,
is that they are organized,
structured, by my notochord
on a starting plane.
This means that if my notochord
is present in its axis
but that in fact, in space,
its function is shifted,
the entire system is shifted.
Understand that we can have a structure
perfectly straight, but in fact, on a plane
of energy, its function is over there.
This means that the notochord is not a structure.
It is a function.
Do you understand? And this is really
important. Because if you take it
as a structure,
you will be in the structure.
But if you understand it as a function,
you will gain its strengths
and its responses.
It’s the mental image, the space.
and the eye.